Indian Neck Folk Festival collection, 1961-2015
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings, 1961-2014
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1977, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR037)
    Cassette 3 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Rick and Lorraine Lee, Bob Franke, Debby McClatchy, John Kaynor, Jonathan Eberhart, Cliff Haslam, Tom McHenry, Eleanor Ellis, and Plumber's Friend.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1977, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR038)
    Cassette 4 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Don Duncan and Art, Kathy, and Tim, Priscilla Herdman, Dave Olive, and Barbara Carns.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1977, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR045)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Paul Cadwell, classical banjo.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1977, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR046)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival dance, Saturday night.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1978, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR047)
    Cassette 1 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Reed Martin and Wally McNauw, Bruce Hutton and Tom McHenry, Captail Kendall Morse, Joan Bronfman and Neal MacMillan, Howie Bursen, Joan Sprung, Matty Levine, Dwayne Thorpe, Maggi Peirce, and Allan Block and Mike Rivers.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1978, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR048)
    Cassette 2 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Allan Block, Rich and Lorraine Lee, Bog Savages, Tom Gibney and friends, Helen Schneyer, and the Bluegrass Bishops.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1978, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR049)
    Cassette 3 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Mike Rivers, Bob Franke and Barbara Carns, Dr. Kilner, Cathy Spencer and Neil Rossi, Lisa Null and Bill Shute, Mark Gilston, Cliff Haslam and David Jones.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1978, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR050)
    Cassette 4 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Cliff Haslam and David Jones, Bruce Hutton, Jacky Spector, Kevin McElroy with Jay Smith and Mark Robinson, Dick Levine, Roy Berkeley, Robin Carns, Debby McClatchy, Mark Adomski, Dave Olive, Lars Hanslin, and the Hummingbirds.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1978, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR051)
    Cassette 5 of 5. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Jonathan Eberhart.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR039)
    Cassette 1 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Joan Sprung, Sara Grey, Allan Block, M. Rivers, Irene Herman, George Balderose, Roy Berkeley and Woodbridge, and Ed Trickett.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR040)
    Cassette 2 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Ed Trickett, Levines, Jug Band (Eberhart, Olive, Hutton), Neal MacMillan and Joanie Bronfman, Mary Callahan, and Rumplestiltskin.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR041)
    Cassette 3 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Jake Walton and Lees, Irene Saletan, Bob Franke, Stan Rogers, Jack Hume, Jonathan Eberhart, Sedalia String Band, and Saul Broudy.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR042)
    Cassette 4 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Saul Broudy, Bruce Hutton, Kevin McElroy, Sharon Pynel, Jay Smith, Truck Carter, Forbes and Comer (Mac B. and April), Ellen Bossom, Jim Stevenson, Dave Kaynor, Tim Woodbridge, and Kendall Morse.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR043)
    Cassette 5 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Lisa Null, Sandy and Caroline Paton, George Ward, Debby McClatchy, Lucy Simpson, Mark Gilston, Kathy Westra, and Joe Hickerson.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR044)
    Cassette 6 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Joe Hickerson (and Kathy Westra), Jack Hudson, Tom McHenry, Bob Stuart, Tim Woodbridge, Dave Kaynor, and Strathspey (Dave Olive) et. al.
  - Broken String Band concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR208)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR203)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival Sunday concert featuring Ken Morse, Lisa Null, the Patons, George Ward, Debby McClatchy, Lucy Simpson, Mark Gilston, Kathy Westra, and Joe Hickerson.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR052)
    Cassette 1 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring April McQuillen, Joan Sprung and Sara Grey, Allan Block, Irene Herman, Mike Rivers, George Balderose, Maggi and Hank Peirce, Roy Berkeley and Tim Woodbridge, and Ed Trickett.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR053)
    Cassette 2 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Ed Trickett, Levines with Marty Sprung, Dr. Kilmer's Jug Band (Dave Olive, Tom McHenry, Bruce Hutton, Jonathan Eberhart), Joan Bronfman and Neil MacMillan with Ed Trickett, Murray Callahan and John Krumm, and Paul Cadwell (secretly recorded).
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR054)
    Cassette 3 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Jake Walton, Rick and Lorraine Lee, Irene Saleton, Bob Franke, John Hue, Paul Cadwell, and Jonathan Eberhart.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR055)
    Cassette 4 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Bruce Hutton, Sharon and Kevin McElroy, Jay Smith, Truck Carter, McQuillen and Limber, Ellen Bossom, Jim Stephenson, Dave Kaynor and Mickey McCloskey, Tim Woodbridge, Jerry Devokaitis, Mickey McCloskey, Ken Morse, and Lisa Null.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR056)
    Cassette 5 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Lisa Null, Saul Broudy, Sara Grey, Caroline Paton, Truck Crouteau, Sandy Paton, George Ward, Debby McClatchy, Lucy Simpson, Mark Gilston, and Kathy Westra.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1979, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR057)
    Cassette 6 of 6. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Joe Hickerson (and Kathy Westra), Jack Hudson, Tom McHenry, Bob Stuart, Tim Woodbridge, Dave Kaynor, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR058)
    Cassette 1 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Woodbridge, Devokaitis, etc., George Balderose, Allan Block, Maggi Peirce, Cathy Fink, Sedalia Trio, Barbara Carns, Roy Berkeley, and Lisa Neustadt.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR059)
    Cassette 2 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Lisa Neustadt, Double Decker String Band, Neil MacMillan and Joanie Bronfman, April, Bob and Pete, David Jones, Kate Spencer and Tom Sample, Helen Schneyer, Lee Bryant, and Paul Cadwell.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR060)
    Cassette 3 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Northwind, Jonathan Eberhart, Cliff Haslam, Snakes in the Bluegrass (with Captain America and the Bluegrass Patriots), Ken Sweeny, Cindy Kallett, Bob Stewart, and Margaret MacArthur.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR061)
    Cassette 4 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Jonathan King (clog dance), Craig Johnson, and Mark Surgies.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR062)
    Cassette 1 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR063)
    Cassette 2 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR064)
    Cassette 3 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording.
  - Broken String Band concert, October 11, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR210)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Harrisburg Area Community College. The Broken String Band, with Ray Wald, Tim Finley and George Ward, from Ithaca, N.Y.
  - Debby McClatchy concert, November 8, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR213)
    2nd Indian Neck Folk Music sponsored concert at Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - "Nowell Sing We Clear" concert, December 13, 1980, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR209)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Harrisburg Community College. Concert featuring John Roberts, Tony Barrand, Fred Bruenig, and Steve Woodruff.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR065)
    Cassette 1 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring New England Tradition (April and Bob McQuillen), Meadow Muffin String Band, Cliff Haslam, Bob Stuart, Craig Johnson, Helen Schneyer, Allan Block, Neil Rossi, Matt Weinberger, Cathy Fink, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR066)
    Cassette 2 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Cathy Fink, Kathy Westra Hickerson, Denny and Donna Clifford, Denny and Tim Woodbridge, Sandy and Caroline Paton, Neal MacMillan, Dave Olive, Joan Sprung and Sara Grey, Eleanor Ellis, Jonathan Eberhart, Rick and Lorraine Lee, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR067)
    Cassette 3 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Smellmore Brothers and Rose, Jonathan Eberhart, Neil Rossi, Tom McHenry, Bob McQuillen, Leo Kratzner, Dave Olive, Mark Gilston, Mike Rivers, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR068)
    Cassette 3, set 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Smellmore Brothers and Rose, Jonathan Eberhart, Neil Rossi, Tom McHenry, Bob McQuillen, Leo Kratzner, Dave Olive, Mark Gilston, Mike Rivers, David Jones, Sandy Sheehan, Art Bryan, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR069)
    Cassette 2, set 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Kathy Hickerson, Denny and Donna Clifford, Denny with Tim Woodbridge, Sandy and Caroline Paton with Dave Olive, Joan Sprung and Sara Grey, Eleanor Ellis, Neal MacMillan, Joan Sprung, Mark Gilston, Jonathan Eberhart, Dave Olive, Rick and Lorraine Lee, Jack Hume, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR070)
    Cassette 1, set 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring New England Tradition, Kate Spencer, Pete Peterson, Meadow Muffin String Band, Cliff Haslam, Craig Johnson, Helen Schneyer, Jonathan Eberhart, Allan Block, Neil Rossi, Matt Weinberger, and Cathy Fink.
  - Dance with John Krumm, January 11, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR216)
    Dance with John Krumm, caller. Tracy's family band at Harrisburg Area Community College. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival with a grant from the Pennsylvania Council on the Arts.
  - Helen Schneyer concert, February 14, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR214)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert at Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Helen Schneyer concert, February 14, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR228)
  - The Vanaver Caravan, music to dances, March 14, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR227)
    Music dances to some dances. Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert at Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Dwayne Thorpe concert, April 11, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR219)
    Cassette 1 of 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival Concert Series concert at Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Dwayne Thorpe concert, April 11, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR220)
    Cassette 2 of 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival Concert Series concert at Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Gordon and Glenn concert, April 19, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR225)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Parts 1 and 3.
  - Gordon and Glenn concert, April 19, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR226)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Parts 2 and 4.
  - Rick and Lorraine Lee concert, May 21, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR217)
  - Rick and Lorraine Lee concert, May 21, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR218)
  - Sunday night concert, September 27, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR211)
    Eisteddfod, Barbara Carns, and Phillipe Bruneau with Dorothy Hogan.
  - Del McCoury and the Dixie Pals concert, October 3, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR215)
    Cassette 1 of 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert at Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Del McCoury and the Dixie Pals concert, October 3, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR223)
    Cassette 2 of 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert at Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Mike Seeger concert, November 7, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR221)
  - Mike Seeger concert, November 7, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR222)
  - Bill Staines concert, December 5, 1981, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR224)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR071)
    Cassette 1 of 5.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR072)
    Cassette 2 of 5.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR073)
    Cassette 3 of 5.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR074)
    Cassette 4 of 5.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR075)
    Cassette 5 of 5.
  - Tony Trischka Band concert, January 23, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR229)
  - Tony Trischka Band concert, January 23, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR230)
  - Double Decker String Band concert, February 6, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR231)
  - Double Decker String Band concert, February 6, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR232)
  - Paton Family concert, February 20, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR233)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert at Harrisburg Area Community College. Sandy and Caroline Paton, and Robin and Dave.
  - Mick Moloney and Eugene O'Donnell concert, March 6, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR234)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival sponsored concert at Harrisburg Area Community College.Mick Moloney and Eugene O'Donnell with step dancer Donny Golden.
  - Gordon Bok and Glenn Jenks concert, April 3, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR235)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival Concert Series concert at Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Ed Trickett concert, September 18, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR240)
    Concert at Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Ed Trickett concert, September 18, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR241)
  - Dulcimer workshop with Lorraine Lee, October 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR236)
    Cassette 1 of 2. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. "Our house on Wyatt Rd. prior to her concert at Harrisburg Area Community College."
  - Dulcimer workshop with Lorraine Lee, October 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR238)
    Cassette 2 of 2. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival.
  - Rick and Lorraine Lee concert, October 16, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR237)
  - Linsey-Woolsey dance, November 21, 1982, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR239)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. A dance with Linsey-Woolsey at Harrisburg Area Community College Center Multi-purpose room. Pete LaBerge, caller. Tim Brown, banjo; Paul Sidlick, guitar; Palmer Turnburke, fiddle.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR076)
    Cassette 1 of 4.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR077)
    Cassette 2 of 4.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR078)
    Cassette 3 of 4.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR079)
    Cassette 4 of 4.
  - Sparky Rucker concert, February 19, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR252)
    Cassette 1 of 2. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival.
  - Sparky Rucker concert, February 19, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR253)
  - Mick Moloney and Eugene O'Donnell concert, March 19, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR242)
    Cassette 1 of 2. Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, mandolin) and Eugene O'Donnell (violin) with step dancer Donny Golden in concert for Indian Neck Folk Festival. Susquehanna, Harrisburg. Sound and recording by Gift Horse Studios, Harrisburg, PA.
  - Mick Moloney and Eugene O'Donnell concert, March 19, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR243)
    Cassette 2 of 2. Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar, mandolin) and Eugene O'Donnell (violin) with step dancer Donny Golden in concert for Indian Neck Folk Festival. Susquehanna, Harrisburg. Sound and recording by Gift Horse Studios, Harrisburg, PA.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 25, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR267)
    Cassette 1 of 2. Friday night concert featuring Swinging on the Gate, Linda Goss, and Caryl P. Weiss.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 25, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR255)
    Cassette 2 of 2. Friday concert with Mick Moloney, Eugene O'Donnell, and Joe and Antoinette McKenna.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 26, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR254)
    Saturday evening concert featuring George Balderose, Old World Folk Band, Saul Broudy, Paul Cadwell, Tom Juravich, and the Mill Creek Cloggers accompanied by Linsey-Woolsey.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 26, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR256)
    Saturday evening concert with Paul Cadwell.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 26, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR260)
    Sea songs workshop. Work and labor songs workshop.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 26, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR263)
    End of sea songs workshop. Work and labor songs workshop.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 26, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR269)
    Blues workshop with Simon Bronner, Saul Broudy, John Pearse, Ken Perlman, and Karl Williams.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 26, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR270)
    Banjo workshop featuring Bob Hartman-Berrier (host), Tim Brown, Debby McClatchy, John LaRose, Mick Moloney, John Pearse, and Ken Perlman.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 26, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR271)
    Unusual instruments workshop featuring Ron Buchanan, Debby McClatchy, and Antoinette McKenna.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 26, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR272)
    Classical banjo concert with Tim Brown and Paul Cadwell.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 26, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR273)
    The Irish Tradition (workshop) featuring Mick Moloney, Eugene O'Donnell, Joe and Antoinette McKenna, Ken Perlman, Dan Duggan, and Debby McClatchy.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 26, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR276)
    Singer-Songwriter workshop with Ray Owen, Dan Duggan, Chris Farrell, Tom Juravich, Caryl P. Weiss, and Karl Williams.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR257)
    Storytellers: Richard Ezell, and Sandy Pomerantz.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR258)
    Patchwork Storytellers: Sandy Lewis, and Tom Coughlin.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR259)
    Gospel workshop: John LaRose, John Pearse, Mary Faith Rhoads. Harmonies and Choruses: Tom Jurvich, John LaRose, David Hildebrand.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR261)
    Old-Time music and songs with Bob Hartman-Berrier, Martha Burns, Tom Juravich, Debby McClatchy, Ken Perlman, and "Linsey-Woolsey," "Swinging on the Gate."
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR262)
    Legends and folk songs: Ken Thigpen.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR264)
    Guitar workshop with Ken Perlman, Martha Burns, and Ray Owen.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR265)
    Country music workshop with Saul Broudy, Martha Burns, Debby McClatchy, Ray Owen, and Caryl P. Weiss.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR266)
    Childrens' Concert with Linda Goss, Dan Duggan, David and Ginger Hildebrand, Karl Williams, and Les Zeiders with puppets.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR268)
    Dulcimer and guitar styles workshop.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR274)
    Excerps from Fiddle Styles workshop, featuring Bob Hartman-Berrier, Ron Buchanan, Pam DeWald, Stan Greene, Donna Isaacs, Eugene O’Donnell, and John Winship.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR275)
    Topical/Women's songs workshop, featuring Caryl P. Weiss, Saul Broudy, Chris Farrell, Debby McClatchy, Ray Owen, John Pearse, Mary Faith Rhoads, and Karl Williams.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR277)
    Fiddle Styles workshop, featuring Bob Hartman-Berrier, Ron Buchanan, Pam DeWald, Stan Greene, Donna Isaacs, Eugene O'Donnell, and John Winship.
  - John McCutcheon concert, April 16, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR248)
    Concert at Harrisburg Area Community College, sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Sound by Gift Horse Studios.
  - John McCutcheon concert, April 16, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR249)
  - John McCutcheon children's concert, April 16, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR250)